Finding Aid for the Actors' Laboratory Records LSC.1064
UCLA Library Special Collections
Actors' Laboratory records
1941-1949
UCLA Library Special Collections
Actors' Laboratory, Inc.
LSC.1064
7.5 Linear Feet (15 boxes)
The Actors' Laboratory of Hollywood was a non-profit professional theater and school which existed from 1941-52. The collection includes financial and legal records, material regarding curriculum, enrollment, policies, and scholarships, minutes from executive board and committee meetings, memos, correspondence, a scrapbook with newsclippings, and notes on the history of the Lab.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Delia Salvi, 1969.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942302933606533
Biography
The Actors' Laboratory of Hollywood was a non-profit professional theater and school which existed from 1941-52.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of business records and materials on productions of the Actors' Laboratory of Hollywood. Includes financial and legal records, material regarding curriculum, enrollment, policies, and scholarships, minutes from executive board and committee meetings, memos, correspondence, a scrapbook with newsclippings, and notes on the history of the Lab. Much of the correspondence is with the Veteran's Administration. Also includes photographs and other materials of productions, including The Inspector General, The Wizard of Oz, All My Sons, A Bell for Adano, Abe Lincoln in Illinois, Trial By Jury, Juno and the Paycock, Peer Gynt (script and score), and Volpone (technical notes on production).
Photographs.; Theatrical companies -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives.; Actors' Laboratory, Inc.--Archives
- Photographs
  - Inspector General.
    - Opened at Las Palmas Theatre. Hollywood, California., Tuesday, October 8 n.d.; (33) black and white photographs (8 × 10) Some photographs folded. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Summary of Play's Origin by Serge Bertensson., n.d.; (67) black and white photographs (8 × 10) (5) small photographs in an Envelope. Summary paper is yellowing, adhesive tape on verso of photographs loose, yellowing. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Home of the Brave (Las Palmas)., n.d.; (63) black and white photographs (8 × 10) (5) Charcoal Reproductions, 1 negative approximately 4 × 5. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Shoemaker's Holiday., n.d.; (1) black and white photograph (8 × 10). (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Noah., n.d.; (16) black and white photographs (4 × 5) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rising of the Moon., n.d.; (4) black and white photographs (8 × 10) Corners on some photographs are torn. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Red Peppers., n.d.; (2) 8 × 10 black and white photos, (2) 5 × 7 black and white photographs. Corner on one photograph is torn. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Wizard of Oz (Las Palmas)., n.d.; (7) 8 × 10 black and white photographs. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Summer Comes to the Diamond., (2) 8 × 10 black and white photographs. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lilliom., n.d.; (30) black and white photos, approximately 4 × 5, (1) 8 × 10 black and white photograph. Some photographs are cut slightly smaller. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pound on Demand & the Bear., (8) 5 × 7 black and white photographs. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 27 Wagon Loads of Cotton., n.d.; (1) 8 × 10 black and white photograph. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Last of My Solid Gold Watches., n.d.; 6) 8 × 10 black and white photographs. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pictures on Lecture Series of March of Drama., 1949.; (14) 8 × 10 black and white photographs. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    General
    Original File Label Reads: (Fall) First Series - Pictures on Lecture Series.
  - On the Evils of Tobacco., n.d.; (1) 5 × 7 black and white photograph. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Volpone., n.d.; (11 × 14) black and white photographs. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Three Men on A Horse., n.d.; (10) 4 × 5 black and white photographs and (14) 8 × 10 black and white photographs. Some photographs are glued to front & back of torn yellowing ripped paper. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Volpone (3rd production)., n.d.; 43 (8 × 10) black and white photographs. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - To the Living., n.d.; (2) 8 × 10 black and white photographs. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Mooney's Kids Don't Cry., n.d.; 4 (11 × 14) black and white photographs of the production (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Yellow Jack., n.d.; (1) 8 × 10 black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The End of the Beginning., 7 (11 × 14) black and white photographs (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Zoning photos, 1945.; (8) Zoning Picture Negatives. Negatives are in small white paper bag. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Cause of It All., n.d.; 18 (8 × 10) black and white photographs (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Ted Sally Caricatures., n.d.; (45) black and white Portraits (5 × 7) and three sets of negatives, and (43) black and white Caricature Portraits (8 × 10). Yellowing and torn little bags containing negatives. File created by collator. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Cause of It All., n.d.; 3 black and white photographs(11 × 14) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Roman Bohnen (Twig is Bent) and Night Music., (8) black and white photographs (4 × 6) and (6) black and white photographs (8 × 10). (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Juno and the Paycock., 3 black and white photographs (8 × 10) and 5 black and white photographs (11 × 14). (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - All My Sons., n.d.; (6) black and white photographs (8 × 10). (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified & The Mask., n.d.; 3 (11 × 14) black and white photographs of Lloyd Bridges, 2 photographs of The Mask, others unidentified. Some creased photographs. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - A Bell for Adano., n.d.; (21) black and white photographs (8 × 10). (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Trial by Jury., n.d.; 3 black and white photographs. One photograph is torn. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Actor's Lab Picnic., 1948.; (17) black and white photographs. Yellowing adhesive tape, some photographs folded. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Portrait of A Madonna with Jessica Tandy., 3 black and white photographs. One photograph is creased & torn. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Abe Lincoln in Illinois., n.d.; (4) black and white photographs. One (7 × 9) photo, three (8 × 10) photographs. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Plant in the Sun., n.d.; 8 black and white photographs. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - All You Need is One Good Break., n.d..; (14) black and white photographs (8 × 10). One photograph has hole in it. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - All Cultural Levels Eat Here., n.d.; (10) black and white photographs (8 × 10) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Awake and Sing., 40 black and white photographs (8 × 10). Two small newspaper advertisement strips. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Awake & Sing (Windsor Theatre)., 1 black and white photograph (5 × 3), 7 black and white photographs (8 × 10) (2 Duplicate Contact Sheets). (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Dragon., n.d.; 39 black and white photographs (8 × 10). (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Scope and Contents
    One Torn Out Cartoon from the New Yorker.
  - The Great Man's Whiskers., n.d.; 5 black and white photographs (8 × 10). (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Freight., n.d.; 9 black and white photographs (8 × 10) Some photographs have old yellowing tape on edges. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Declaration Party., n.d.; 38 black and white photographs (8 × 10) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lab Personnel & Building photographs., n.d.; 1 black and white photograph (8 × 10), (8) (4 × 5) photos, envelope with assorted small photographs. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Another Part of the Forest., n.d.; 4 black and white photographs (8 × 10). (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Exuberanza., n.d.; 10 black and white photographs (5 × 7), 25 black and white photographs (8 × 10). (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Aboard., 1944.; 3 black and white photographs (4 × 3). (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Aria De Capo., n.d.; 2 black and white photographs (8 × 10). (Spelling is unclear). (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - The Banker's Daughter., n.d.; 10 black and white photographs (8 × 10) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Plant in the Sun., n.d.; 4 (11 × 14) black and white photographs (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Declaration and Musart., 1947-1950.; Yellowing Carbon Papers. File created by collator. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Correspondence, notes, contracts, lists, re pre-production, cost breakdowns, union status of cast.
- Original Costume Drawings., n.d.; 8 original painted drawings showing various costumes. Some papers are torn at edge. File created by collator. (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Report to Workshop Members., January 16, 1946. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Outline, speech, meeting minutes, notes, re tryout procedures, background information on The lab, rules and regulations for actors and members, agenda. Original File Label Reads: Report to Workshop Members
- Tarcai Memos from Mary Tarcai re Actor's Lab Theatre miscellaneous., 1947. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Schedules, past correspondence, notes, pamphlet, 1948-1949. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  re American Educational Theatre Association, Constitution of the Southern California American Educational Theatre Association; agenda and schedule.
- Class Personnel, Summer 48. Student Enrollment Summer Session, 1948. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- School policy, body training for actors, objectives of courses, evaluations., 1948.; Loose carbon papers, some creased. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Touring Repertory Project., 1947-1948. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, memo, handwritten letter, re touring workshop repertory project.
- Curriculum & Objectives., n.d.; File created by collator. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Booklet re curriculum, method of instruction, objectives, general school purpose and policies.
- Scholarships
  - Ben Bogeaus Scholarship., 1946-1947.; Some carbon papers are creased. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, Western Union Telegram re Ben Bogeaus Scholarship.
  - Dick Fiske Scholarship., 1945-1948. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, memo, notes, story about Dick Fiske and the Dick Fiske Scholarship.
  - Exchange Scholarships., 1946-1947. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Correspondence re Exchange Scholarships.
  - Quinn Scholarship., 1947-1948. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Correspondence re Anthony & Katherine Quinn Scholarship.
- Labor Day Picnic 1947., Some yellowing, torn, creased papers. Contains one side of old file folder with handwritten notes. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Correspondence, receipts, lists of attendees and members of Actor's Lab Workshop, re Labor Day Picnic at Lloyd Bridges Beachhouse.
- Television Plays., 1942-1947.; Paper is Brittle, Yellow, Some Torn, Paperclip Marks. Contains some very small news paragraphs, needs envelope for these. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Newspaper Clippings re Actor's Lab Workshop, Veterans, Television Plays, Various productions.
- Lab Statement of Policy adopted by Board., 1941-1945.; Typed carbon papers. Carbon paper is yellowing. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Tenney Subpoena, News., 1944-1948.; Some torn papers. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  News releases, Correspondence, memos, news re censorship, Senator Tenney's subpoena of Roman Bohnen and others in an attack against Free Theatre.
- History - Lab., 1946.; Typed notes. Yellowing carbon papers. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- General correspondence., 1942-1949.; Yellowing edges on some papers. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, notes, re Actor's Lab Events, parties, picnics, discrimination attacks.
- Tenney Correspondence Received by Lab., 1948.; Papers are yellow, brown, torn. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Correspondence, telegrams re fight against Senator Tenney and censorship, discrimination, Committee on Un-American Activities, Thomas Committee attack on Film Industry.
- Executive Board materials
  - Executive Board minutes., 1942-1944. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    News bulletin, minutes, notes, correspondence re Executive Board of Actor's Lab.
  - Executive Board., 1946-1947. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, telegram, re Executive Board.
  - Minutes of Executive Board, Notes., 1941-1942.; Some faded, yellow, brittle, torn papers. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Duplicate Minutes of Executive Board Meetings., 1946.; Some faded, yellow, brittle papers. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of Executive Board Meetings., 1947. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Duplicate Minutes of Executive Board Meetings, 1947. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes., 1948-1949. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Attendance records, accounts payable, back salaries, handwritten notes. Original File Label Reads: Executive Board Minutes November 9th, 1948 - Duplicate Work File.
  - Executive Board Minutes., 1948-1949. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Minutes of Executive Board Meetings, Agenda, Handwritten Notes. Contains Uncashed Check
  - Executive Board minutes, correspondence, minutes of meeting with Paul Robeson re negro actor., 1945.; Fragile pages. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Robeson's remarks. Contains names and home addresses of Board Members.
- Wires. Telegrams, Congratulations., 1942-1948.; Yellow, brittle, some torn. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Tenney., 1948.; Water damage on address labels. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Lists of names and addresses, telephone numbers of audience sponsors, address labels. Some material may be confidential.
- War Work of Actor's Lab., 1945-1947. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, report of Actor's Lab War Record, gratitude from Red Cross, American Veteran's Committee.
- 1948 Fact-Finding Committee Minutes, Report, some history of the Actor's Lab Workshop & Theatre, agenda of Actor's Lab Fact Finding Committee, statement of policy, membership, finances. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Cheryl Crawford., 1945. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Correspondence from Bohnen to Cheryl Crawford re early opinion, hopes for Actor's Lab.
- Lab Housing Information., 1940-1947. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Brochure for steel products, correspondence, re new site building & construction philosophy and needs.
- Permits., 1942-1946.; Edges of some paper torn. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Police permits, fire safety permits, city licenses. 1642 N. Las Palmas Ave.
- Harold Clurman., 1946. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Correspondence re Harold Clurman & Bohnen.
- William Kent., 1946-1947. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Receipts re William Kent Insurance and Actor's Lab.
- Zoning, Taxes, Licences., 1946-1947.; Old tape yellowing, edges torn on some paper. file labeled by collator. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Receipts, permits, licenses, postage permits re Actor's Lab.
- War shows., 1943-1944. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Newspaper clippings, telegram, Correspondence re various productions overseas, one photograph (4 × 3).
- Theatre Fund - Bohnen., 1949. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Correspondence, telegrams, names and addresses of Executive Board, condolences re death of Roman Bohnen. Contains blank envelopes and announcements for memorial service, some material may be confidential.
- Roman Bohnen Memorial., 1949. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Receipt for advertising in the Hollywood Reporter, phone rental for Memorial Service for Roman Bohnen. Original File Label Reads: Roman Bohnen Memorial Assembly Paid Bills.
- Tenney Theatre Council., 1948.; Yellow, brittle papers. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Correspondence, telegrams, speeches, drafts, notes re Actor's Lab Defense Against Senator Tenney and State Un-American Activities attack.
- Actor's Lab, Incorporated. Bylaws., 1945. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Official Bylaws including name, purpose, membership, management of the Actor's Laboratory, Incorporated.
- Constitution - (B)., 1946; Contains duplicate. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Constitution and By-Laws of Actor's Laboratory, Incorporated.
- Peer Gynt Script, Score., n.d.; Fragile papers, needs conservation work. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Peer Gynt Script, Costume Changes, Musical Score, characters in scene, work sketches, plot. Original label also read: Running schedule, musical score, floor, lights and plans.
- Constitution (C)., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Volpone - Technical Data., n.d.; Yellowing carbon papers. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Prop list, costumes, setting, lights, scenery, notes.
- State Department of Education., 1946-1949. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, schedules, curriculum outline, school policy, re request for State Board of Education to approve 18-month term, termination of contract with Veteran's administration, all materials submitted to State Board of Education. Contains List of Executive Board Members, names & addresses; may be confidential.
- Constitution (AA)., n.d.; Copies. (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Financial materials
  - Finances Tenancy agreement, notes, screen actor advertising contract, tuition income, water & electric bill receipts., 1941-1942. 1941-1943. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, Statements of Income & Expense, cash receipts & disbursements., 1944-1945. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Statements of Revenue & Expenses, Financial Statements., 1946. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, Revenue & Expenses., 1947. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, Accounts Receivable, Balance Sheets., 1948-1949.; Top papers torn & fragile. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statement, Accounts Payable, notes., 1948. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Statement Income & Expense., 1946-1948. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Statements of Income & Expense, Explanatory Statement, Monthly Budget.
  - Monthly Statements, correspondence, balance sheets, Statement of Income & Expense, Tuition Income, Income from productions., 1949. 1948-1949. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Employment & Tax-Employees., 1945-1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, tax forms, claims. Confidential materials.
  - Claims filed Employment Department., 1947-1950. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Tax forms, claims. confidential materials.
  - Tax Forms & Information., 1945. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Bank Reconciliation., 1950. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Bank Reconciliation Statements, Payroll Account.
  - Lab General Account - Checks., 1948-1950.; Envelope Torn. File created by collator. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    1950 Returned Checks, Actors Lab General Account June 1948 Checks.
  - Check Stubs, Destroyed Checks. Check stubs 1948-1949, destroyed Checks and stubs 1949., File created by collator. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bank Statements, Checks. Returned Checks-Theatre Wing account, All My Sons Tally Sheets, Bank Statements., 1948-1950.; File created by collator. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Commercial Account Passbooks. Actor's Lab various accounts' passbooks (blue leather covers), Theatre wing account, Roman Bohnen Memorial account, declaration account, Dick Fiske Memorial Fund., 1948-1949.; File created by collator. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Payroll Account. Deposit Slips, Checks re Actor's Lab payroll account, tax withholding statements. Confidential., 1947-1948. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Payroll account receipts, checks. Records, logs, stubs, passbooks, checks cancelled re Actor's Lab, Ben Bogeaus, Richard Fiske Memorial Fund, Declaration Account., 1947-1950. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Payroll account, other accounts. Records, stubs, checks cancelled re Actor's Lab, Richard Fiske Memorial Fund, payroll account, declaration account, Theatre Wing account., 1947-1949. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Blank Actor's Lab checks., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cancelled Checks., 1948-1949.; Contains original rubber bands. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Check Stubs & Statements., 1947.; 12 Actor's Lab Check stub booklets, 5 envelopes with bank statements. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Check Stubs & Statements., 1946-1948.; Check book register w/ stubs, bank books, bank statements. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Tax Forms & Petty Cash Receipts. Petty cash receipts, state copies of #599 forms not filed because no single employee earned over $3000. Confidential., 1945-1946. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bank of America
    - Bank of America Bank Statements., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Bank of America Bank Statements., 1944-1945. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bank of America Bank Statements., 1944-1945. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Bank of America. Bank Receipts, Payment Record., 1947-1950. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Employees Compensation Records 1945, Depositors Record of Checks, Form 729 Amusement Tax Returns, Bank Notes & Loan Papers., 1944-1948. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bank Statements & Check Records, Stubs., 1946-1949. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Bookkeeping Data. Bank books, check stubs, bank statements California Bank., 1941-1944. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Payroll Ledgers., 1948-1949.; File created by collator. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Payroll Ledgers, Accounts Payable Ledgers, Record of Purchases 1949, Salaries on Mamlock. Confidential., 1949-1950; File created by collator. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Large black book of money receipts., 1944-1945. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - General Ledger Accounts, production, expense account, payroll account, assets & liabilities., 1945-1948. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Check stubs, declaration acct petty cash, dragon petty cash., 1947-1948.; Torn, yellow envelopes. File created by collator. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - General Ledger accounts, bank, income and expense, Theatre Wing account, description of accounts, cash accounts, check register., 1945-1948. (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Report to State Board of Education., 1946-1949. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, curriculum outline presented to State Board of Education for Approval of 18-month Term, Veteran's Training Program, physical facilities of school. Contains names & addresses of executive board members; may be confidential.
- Internal Revenue Correspondence., 1945-1946. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Correspondence, Commissioner of Internal Revenue.
- Correspondence, Constitution & By-Laws of Actor's Laboratory, envelope with Quorum Resolution ballots., 1948. 1947-1948. (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Insurance., 1944-1949. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Correspondence re Insurance Coverage, Legal document re Workman's Compensation Case, Forms.
- Hollywood Film Society., 1947.; File created by collator. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  One spiral notebook entitled Actor's Lab Workshop Hollywood Film Society Showings, balance sheet.
- Legal Records & Correspondence., 1943-1946. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, fire permits, insurance endorsements.
- Two Scripts - Free Treat and The Farewell Supper., 1946. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  File created by collator.
- Report to State Board of Education., 1947. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Correspondence, notes, re approval of technical course, description of technical course, schedule.
- Script of play entitled The House of Bernard Alba by Frederico Garcia Lorca., n.d.; File created by collator. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- State Department of Education., 1945. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Correspondence re training of veterans, faculty, schedule of classes.
- Newsletters, memos from Actor's Workshop to Executive Board., 1947. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- New Teachers Class., 1946-1947. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Typed descriptions of teachers' courses on acting, philosophies of acting.
- 20th Century Fox (4 folders)
  - Contracts., 1945-1947. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, contracts with Twentieth Century Fox re acting personnel.
  - Paid Memos, Receipts of Payment by Fox to Actor's Lab Workshop., December 16, 1946. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Paid Memos, Receipts for Tuition for Actor's Lab Workshop., April 6, 1946. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Interview Questionnaires for actors, names & addresses of actors from Fox., 1945. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Materials May Be Confidential.
- Promotion-Early Lab Classes., 1941-1942.; Some papers are brittle, torn, folded, brown, yellow. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, notes, brochure, drafts re promotion & early lab classes.
- Universal Pictures (4 folders)
  - Correspondence re Joan Fulton, Universal Pictures., 1947-1948. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Contractual Agreements - Universal., 1946-1947. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, notes, re contractual agreements between Actors Lab and Universal Pictures.
  - Universal - Paid ()., 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, receipts for tuition from Universal Pictures.
  - Universal - Paid ()., April 1946 (Box 5, Folder 20)